Guide to the Empire State Pride Agenda records, 1990-2013
Empire State Pride Agenda records, 1990-2013
- Series IV. Audio Visual and Digital Media
  - DVDs
    - Understanding Transgender Issues, 2007; DVD-1206 (Box 13)
      DVD put out by the Human Rights Campaign
    - Alan Van Capelle CCESL Speaker, January 28, 2008; DVD-1359 (Box 13)
    - Governor David Paterson Message to ESPA Spring Dinner, May 14, 2008; DVD-1360 (Box 13)
      RT 5:04
    - NYS Gov. Patterson Calls on State Agencies to Acknowledge Same Sex Marriage, May 29-30, 2008; DVD-1361 (Box 13)
      news recordings
    - NYS Gov. Patterson Calls on State Agencies to Acknowledge Same Sex Marriage, May 29-30, 2008; DVD-1362 (Box 13)
    - Capital Tonight: Marriage Equality in NYS, May 29, 2008; DVD-1363 (Box 13)
      incl. note- "Ross is in 2nd segment of program"
    - Fall Dinner- Backup, 2008; DVD-1364 and 1430 (Box 13)
      Linton Media, RT 08:13
    - Fall Dinner- Master, 2008; DVD-1365 (Box 13)
      Linton Media
    - ESPA 4 Youtube- Spring Dinner videos, 2008; DVD-1366 (Box 13)
    - ESPA 2008 Video, 2008; DVD-1367-1368 (Box 13)
      2 copies
    - In the Life: "Lifesavers", November 2008; DVD-1369 (Box 13)
      Episode 1802
    - Marriage Equality and Religion- Final, April 20, 2009; DVD-1370 (Box 13)
      6'16
    - Marriage Equality and Religion, April 24, 2009; DVD-1371 (Box 13)
    - Governor David Paterson Comments to ESPA, May 11, 2009; DVD-1372 (Box 13)
    - New York State Assembly Session Disks 1-3, May 12, 2009; DVD-1373-1375 (Box 13)
      Same Sex Marriage
    - Winning Equality and Justice for LGBT New Yorkers and Our Families, 2009; DVD-1376-1378 (Box 13)
      News video from first half of 2009; 3 copies
    - ESPA Fall Dinner, October 22, 2009; DVD-1431 (Box 13)
    - ESPA Fall Dinner, October 22, 2009; DVD-1432 (Box 13)
    - ESPA Fall Dinner, October 22, 2009; DVD-1433-1435 (Box 13)
      Camera 1: RT 01:57:09
    - ESPA Fall Dinner, October 22, 2009; DVD-1436-1437 (Box 13)
      Camera 2: RT 01:57:09
    - NYS Senate Session: "Marriage Equality Bill", December 2, 2009; DVD-1379 (Box 13)
    - Marching On, December 18, 2009; DVD-1380-1382 (Box 13)
      RT 03:30; 3 copies
    - Assembly '09 Disks 1-3, 2009; DVD-1383-1385 (Box 13)
    - LGBT Equality and Justice Day 2009: The Time is Now!, 2009; DVD-1386 (Box 13)
    - Empire State Pride, June 16, 2010; DVD-1387 (Box 13)
    - ESPA Fall Dinner, October 14, 2010; DVD-1388-1389 (Box 13)
      RT 01:45:00; 2 copies
    - Miss New York Pageant: Friday Preliminary, 2010; DVD-1390 (Box 13)
    - Miss New York Pageant: Saturday Final, 2010; DVD-1391 (Box 13)
    - Armani Photos, 2011; DVD-1392 (Box 13)
    - Armani Photos, 2011; DVD-1393 (Box 13)
    - ESPA 20th Anniversary Video, May 6, 2011; DVD-1394 (Box 13)
      RT 08:24
    - ESPA 20th Anniversary Video, 2011; DVD-1395; 1203-1204 (Box 13)
      RT 08:30; (3 copies, slightly different labels)
    - 20th Anniversary Video, 2011; DVD-1203-1204 (Box 13)
    - New York State Assembly Session Disk 1, June 15, 2011; DVD-1396 (Box 13)
    - New York State Assembly Session Disk 2, June 15, 2011; DVD-1397 (Box 13)
    - New York State Assembly Sesson Disks 1-4, June 24, 2011; DVD-1398-1401 (Box 13)
    - NYS Senate Session: "Marriage Equality Bill", June 24, 2011; DVD-1402 (Box 13)
    - In the Life: 20th Anniversary Season Premiere, October 2011; DVD-1403 (Box 13)
      Episode 2101
    - Nathan Schaefer Intro Video, Undated; DVD-1200-1202 (Box 13)
    - Anna and David, Undated; DVD-1205 (Box 13)
    - New Yorkers United for Marriage: "Blumenthal", Undated; DVD-1404-1406 (Box 13)
    - New Yorkers United for Marriage: "Vows", Undated; DVD-1407-1409 (Box 13)
    - New Yorkers United for Marriage: Presentation Reel, Undated; DVD-1410-1412 (Box 13)
    - misc. footage concerning marriage, Undated; DVD-1413 (Box 13)
    - ESPA Marriage Ad, Undated; DVD-1414 (Box 13)
    - ESPA Marriage Ad, Undated; DVD-1415 (Box 13)
    - ESPA Spring Dinner Andrew Cuomo Address, Undated; DVD-1416-1417 (Box 13)
      RT 2:40; 2 copies
    - STSO Trailer, Undated; DVD-1418 (Box 13)
    - Tying the Knot: The Union that's Dividing America, Undated; DVD-1419 (Box 13)
    - Assembly Vote on Marriage- clips, Undated; DVD-1420 (Box 13)
    - 2nd Valentine's Day Rally- Marriage Equality, Undated; DVD-1421 (Box 13)
    - Eliot Spitzer Address, Undated; DVD-1422-1424 (Box 13)
    - Lobbying your Legislator, Undated; DVD-1438-1441 (Box 13)
    - Marriage Equality and Religion: The Massachusetts Experience, Undated; DVD-1442-1444 (Box 13)
    - Nathan Schaefer Intro Video, Undated; DVD-1200-1202 (Box 13)
    - Anna and Vincent, Undated; DVD-1205 (Box 13)
    - Understanding Transgender Issues: Donna Rose's Story, Undated; DVD-1206 (Box 13)
    - Joseph Tar (Photo), 2009; DVD-1449 (Box 13)
      Found with photos in Box 22
    - Winter Heat, 2010; DVD-1450 (Box 13)
  - CDs
    - Fall Dinner Powerpoint, 2004; CD-2321 (Box 13)
    - Billy Porter: at the corner of Broadway & soul, 2005; CD-2322 (Box 13)
      Purchased music CD
    - Fall Dinner Powerpoint, 2005; CD-2323 (Box 13)
    - Stand- Original & Acoustic, September 2005; CD-2324 (Box 13)
      Rick
    - ESPA v.6 Join, September 21, 2005; CD-2325 (Box 13)
      Brochures, fonts, logos
    - Pride music, 2006; CD-2326 (Box 13)
    - Buffalo Brunch, 2006; CD-2327 (Box 13)
      Powerpoints and photos
    - Reports, October 20, 2006; CD-2328 (Box 13)
      Excel, PowerPoint, Word
    - Presentation CD, 2002, 2003, 2007; CD-2329 (Box 13)
      Includes "Marriage Mythbusters Albany" 2007 PowerPoint
    - On gay marriage, January 14, 2007; CD-2330 (Box 13)
    - Fall Dinner invite, 2007; CD-2331 (Box 13)
    - Marriage Ambassadors Training Powerpoint, 2007; CD-2332 (Box 13)
    - Equality at Work Powerpoint, 2007; CD-2333 (Box 13)
    - E & J Powerpoint, c. 2007; CD-2384 (Box 13)
    - E & J Final (2), 2007; CD-2385 (Box 13)
    - Rochester Reception photos, 2008; CD-2334 (Box 13)
    - ESPA '08 Mix, 2008; CD-2335 (Box 13)
    - Spring Dinner Powerpoint, 2008; CD-2336 (Box 13)
    - Fall Dinner, 2008; CD-2387 (Box 13)
    - Equality at Work, 2008-2009; CD-2337 (Box 13)
    - State Senate Sign pdf, 2009; CD-2338 (Box 13)
    - Tea Dance photos, 2009; CD-2339 (Box 13)
    - Spring Dinner, May 14, 2009; CD-2340 (Box 13)
    - Spring Dinner program, registration, name tags, 2009; CD-2341 (Box 13)
    - Spring Dinner Powerpoint, May 14, 2009; CD-2342 (Box 13)
    - Spring Dinner Intro Music, 2009; CD-2343 (Box 13)
    - Fall Dinner Jazz Mix, 2009; CD-2344 (Box 13)
    - Fall Dinner Music Cues, 2009; CD-2345 (Box 13)
    - Fall Dinner Music Cues, 2009; CD-2346 (Box 13)
    - TDOR, 2011; CD-2386 (Box 13)
    - Dreamgirls CD for JYC, Undated; CD-2347-2348 (Box 13)
    - Unidentified .wma files, Undated; CD-2349 (Box 13)
    - .tif and unrecognized files, Undated; CD-2350 (Box 13)
    - Family scrapbook submissions, Undated; CD-2351 (Box 13)
      "Binder1.pdf" scans of scrapbook-style submissions of photos and messages for marriage equality
    - Steven Green Inside Cover Ad, Undated; CD-2352 (Box 13)
    - Equality at Work Sponsor Forms, Undated; CD-2353 (Box 13)
    - Pride in the Pulpit- Denise Denato, Undated; CD-2354 (Box 13)
  - Other Media
    - ESPA - Katovitz, 2007; Mini-Cassette TR-10564 (Box 13)
    - Karen Dewitt - NYS Public Radio, August 5, 2002; Cassette TR-10565 (Box 13)
    - Skelos and ESPA Logo, Undated; 3" Floppy FD-55 (Box 13)
    - FDN Center Search, March 22, 2001; 3" Floppy FD-57 (Box 13)